oh yeah we need that we do need that
yeah we don't need that so we have to
figure out why how do we need that but
we need that because we have to short
can but if we just love to count quite a
bit no because then they can't marry
sending stuff I don't think so basically
we have just connected to camera and no
one run or oh but I thought you could
leave the camera plugged in no you sure
I'm pretty sure because the camera is
the one that stands the steam command no
but the camera doesn't sound any command
if it's like not talking to the SDM oh
there's some there's some trick waited
yeah not use that okay I'm pretty sure
because they'd like they were talking
about like the minimum were talking
about the minimum required stuff for the
Vols oh yeah you don't have to talk to
the camera cutting that crew now
actually different crew different firms
the board group George Rodney's power
what they had that means the power he
said no patience ins power from the back
yes yeah so we cannot no I mean I think
we're gonna do like if everything to do
some like you know janky board at the
back plug in
about like Texas this cat right arm like
that yeah oh let's see if anyone
mentions it to see how attempt of scope
these are it's not these diseases a very
dark fast wait why can't I engage her
well because you have enough ability
much power and your brain
America stay plugged into Oh the camera
can stay plugged in and this is today's
this is the oldest not today's model Jim
Gina well there is not really GM G ruff
I mean in a certain sense no I'll be not
being acquired sitting at the back and I
think we'll sell it that plugs in to the
ASEM connector yeah because I wanted to
just be one thing you unplug the SEM
connector you plug it into all right
there we are engaged
got them all feels good
oh yes not the latest but yeah it's not
the latest um you guys saw so the
problem I was having with the model on
our on our drive to the off site it only
exists in the rav4 and we're not exactly
sure why it happens we think it has to
do with the height of the rav4
well
so now it should go in Arizona yeah okay
so now you have to press resume horses
are kept near the camera bugs out on
that thing yeah that's the way Flickr
frame okay so knowing your mother
yeah it is your mother this is not the
new new new it's just in your new it's
probably not the one we're shipping oh
we gotta fix Flickr Fred you have take
your frame yes yeah the Skokie's no it's
good there's no Flickr frame on your ear
yeah sort of like specially specially on
you the new hardware guys which counties
obviously it's the vault some can I
presume it'll stain yeah three seconds
we have a guy from Grand Valley watching
us endeavor Moya ganda God welcome does
it faster net you got it ya know the the
resume uh there is nobody around we
can't sell about we can we can probably
spend the bottom
or the times working time so I would say
party thirty percent of the time okay
okay thanks I'm work they did not go
spamming the resume programmatically no
but we can I think antenna right now
we're driving with a antonella's gray
panda well yeah
I was gonna try doing that yes James
thanks
that autofocus bugs
it's gonna fix their autofocus and the
flickering well the autofocus is uh
I mean I might just be yeah that might
be appropriate actually I don't know
yeah it's like
oh yeah it's like
yay detects for the accelerometer and
then it's like you can turn in the focus
thing GTS I'm guessing is the vault no
we're not we're in a vault right now oh
I hate that's hate that have to press
the button
yeah with spam resume because that's
like sets the state machine and that but
we're running our own crews I don't
understand hmm
we're running our own cruise control you
tell me the accelerate command just
doesn't work if it's no we're running on
our cruise control but they when you
stop the car they go in a special state
that they don't pay the PCI becomes non
responsive unless you press that button
it's not like we do anything they just
least in their acting to the bottom yes
[Music]
did but I'm sure we can figure out like
winning Kings are safe though yeah we
should we should look into that and we
should get those charts to be harder Sam
do that okay oh yeah and I think there's
a lot for it
the Tooting was just like go wrong on
the steering or something well you
needed like the 80 meter this deferred
lose what next burn no this gets
released this print money is the society
bothered it's not well we I want to
drive a little bit new parameters on the
couch
oh you shipped other parameters for the
cars yeah I know I know you do it's good
on these low cars
that was weird what do you do well I was
rolling and it said press resume to move
well probably because he's I can't check
this one he should because it's linked
to the states also as the state preserve
these safety the father reduced the wall
well it's not the safety depend it's
garlic tuning control staff by there is
a whole new safety for steering of Banda
but I think about the safety for
steering by the way
we're good no wobble yeah is it the
model or is it uh it's a mixed model
plus you
some puny
that wasn't nice yes
I feel like we're a little too far too
right to the right
well so we're still having I'm gonna
have all day so one thing that we want
to do for the next for the next three
entities are removing the sitting ankle
offset yeah with the feedback and he
said exactly for the next i think the
breaking feels pretty good the final
point sometimes it does a little there
is basically no wobble with intel we'd
open pilot yeah the heat here the best
actor in the world of course
yeah I think it has to do it they all
said Lerner
yeah I like that
I like the way I like the red how much I
like that go when he is a person of
these stunts together well though
based on it gets ran over based on the
velocity differentials oh yeah that's
right good if I mix right there you see
can I get brighter like brightness
[Music]
I guess modern leader to a two-leg yes
we are it's it's considered in modern
political control
we have different parameters the
different forms yeah and we are gonna
cheaper so every carriage is on delay
and this this week we're gonna ship a
specific parameter for each car
if you're done a premise prime yet it is
it is supported fish Brian yeah GM is
the last of the new cars we're gonna
ship the GM branch the next open pilot
and then we're not gonna be up streaming
any other cars
this is it
I like that it goes up by we control
that goes up by five yeah we've got
other because we control the yes nice
right
yeah goes on high five so yeah when we
change like the speed that you can stop
by if I like the set speed you don't
need to keep rushing forever
let's see this is when the new model
shines yes
this is supercruise quality
supers actually can engage you
and wanting some eat and not anymore now
the new model is real guys look at that
solid those lanes are on their model
yeah we have anything more than yeah
get ready crease chest and fast
now that screams like this purse
super cohesion part before GM
you guys this is really nice we're gonna
lose this doesn't wobble yeah
and you plan to support us a certain
vault sort of thing
unfortunately you need the stupid option
packages yeah so you need the premier
package which still doesn't include
driver confidence - well this is so nice
it's
yeah
you fix the pond you force it yet yes I
do father overshadow but I'm sure yeah I
think it's saturated the control how can
we make it a morning because what yeah
explain why do you remove it well
because no we need it well so I think
what you did but then we need we need
some new things that actually we should
put also for to the author
yeah I gotta move because
[Music]
when playing o ver like manually yeah
you like the comte also to raise about
that jar yeah bitch I worked yeah
because we're a bit banging that time
I'll be uh no we need we need awarding
of the control saturated okay but then
okay I need like more general change
which is fine
[Music]
like oh they're writing yourself
right
the juicer the gym is that weak
yeah it seems we care the better but
that's a requirement to see how I can
okay well I put there even if it comes
off at the wrong times
yeah it's just we need something yeah
I can just ship the Lord like it's it's
like it's one time I didn't I need to
change the thermal torque limit
cars have torque limits guys
a lot better at low speeds which work
basalt or
I don't know
because when you go highly speed that
you to eat that order
our Louis beating would return high
speed because the redlining moment on
the way it's getting your speed for the
same thing for the same again
interesting yeah so I mean I guess
there's some there's a best possible
there's like you know because obviously
it requires time to talk to go to zero
speed oh wait yeah having to good deals
because you have a plan of like static
for infusion and everyone is not gonna
work
I mean yes now there is he works
probably as good as the old one mm-hm
you got it about like a 30 page
okay so asked if we like the finger
everything I don't know oh yeah oh yeah
you really like that that's all that's
that's one of the secrets
Oh your secret economy I know how about
that television hack some other ways
February those are all cancels all PCM
hacks are canceled but if there is going
to be a flash all three flashes are
can't know the only reflex that might be
considered is any Bosch radar reflow it
gets us more data we love data all all
functionality re flashes are canceled
for business reasons not for technical
reasons
bye-bye nice supportive car here comes
to yoga PETA panel oh I mean yeah that
might happen
I'll feel good no my legs well but there
is a whites better is because when
they'll they'll modern when it's
uncertain it was telling to write it's
not like it was trying to take the
Exeter it was just the consequence of I
don't know where to go go right what a
crappy model yeah I can't believe we
shipped it for so long is that the young
fan were here now I'd say she she's on
oh yeah yeah young fan is similar in
loudness to your car racing
year by the fudge doesn't even
turn around the author
I think can't write the tuna isn't the
one that isn't luxury yeah
Jesus a or something I think he doesn't
have some feature that we need
yeah if you gotta eat me up a pilot you
see if it's actually support you if you
can't be supported on
so here's the thing I don't know whether
this turn exceeds limits
yeah I can change it yeah I can change
it but it's gonna be annoying when you
when you write your self it's always
going to throw it but it's fixable I can
probably fix Bart beings today
but by Deniz Easter Easter eggs
yeah look there's two pigs let's do the
Easter egg it's a glitch frame if you
hit the pedal during the glitch frame it
disengages
booting you need a minimum of two
cameras don't do it away with that other
no no no what comes up in one camera
yeah mobile I can do it we can do it
people can die with one eye
so nice so nice look at that
it doesn't cut into turns early anymore
it seems I feel like the old model will
just cut into that turn pushed out a
little still
new model yes it is not even the latest
I know the newer new model is gonna be
even better
yeah
a lot of people from working
it's all part of our new mapping
architecture
guys there's a lot of great stuff coming
unbelievable stuff
now if you have a G app you'll be able
to get it all should we make to make the
GM
the GM draft bill in the back we should
probably make something like well be
nice the Africa like auto switch the
radar power based on the presence of cat
messages simple analog circuit for that
ah
yeah wow that that uh the skyline back
is almost flawless the only real
disengagement switch
in here and there are people who stuff
very soon very soon guys yeah
well although I mean the first of the
unbelievable stuff will be the model
yeah no it's not like you know this
bottle is not it's the same architecture
it's not like radically do we just the
data quality has gone up from fast
that's appendage enough we'll work on
2018 a quarter no were you going to
draft us they're gonna come up with on
you on the job
yeah we both don't worry that
discontinuing the old one yeah
OSHA found of Australis all
yeah I think this is probably
comfortable to the new new autopilot
model I think so
now the volta are not on delay trick
they are it balls are just electric yeah
and the bolts are not supported
is the stopping for red light still I
think there's not a problem with that
yeah yeah we don't want to ship it until
we can make it really reliable we got to
do maps first guys
we're hiring a mapping engineer
the sooner we get back her the sooner
Maps happen
we're monthly you saying max torque
stealin 0xff it can do more really
mottely tell me how can we do more
torque
well I mean this limit is probably a
little lower than they tend to yours I
would say
get that wobble it's more in honde at
least mother has known torque as we
disappointing about its work we're all
over the place
right
fusion of stock car infusion Lusaka I
think it was really moving and get all
the way but oh man
how I was gonna be happy with his drive
back just an improved yeah well he's not
gonna have youth on this we ship today
we can go in Devan I guess
Oh model you get a whole model guys what
you love old model this model has two
problems I think one of them is fixed in
the one that was trained last night in
sharp turns it gives up and goes
straight and a rav4 does Mark know maybe
he just won't get it helps get old old
yeah he's gonna do it stuff should we
make extreme devel it's like to hell but
it gets even more so monthly says we
can't just go I go then 0xff interesting
okay yeah well I took the safety was
saying that if we commend more than that
he's gonna fall Tower I actually never
tried should have tried
one time like why didn't that go oh he
didn't go through review got yeah my
first was oh I was like I was on a hill
okay
sure snap
now this is gonna the shares all the
same protocol category right I'm just
gonna I need to do the marriage but like
that close I just need to hurt them
let's do that what we still have this
corner yeah
what happened there
do not have stereotype available
right well I miss Tito sadness oh yeah
be nice we got our new tools to review
these great things up yeah I got that of
your dish finger got a good old America
put back the large I felt so nice that
I'll have to press the stupid resume
button would you would you mother
okay if it's there
maybe
cool
definitely shippable
i supercruise quality on the highway
guys almost if anything he was available
I think ISM we wouldn't have who never
had super Crowley's the for the entire
driver you know I was no it was no part
of that time the Super's development I
think cool
all right thanks focus o
0ff is to never fault limit it can fault
above that Oh